philippinepetfinder.com 2013-11-03

# Privacy Policy

Philippinepetfinder.com has established this Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with what we have to treat your Personal Information. Philippine Pet Finder respects each individual’s right to personal privacy. Philippine Pet Finder does not collect personally identifiable data from individual unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. This means that Philippine Pet Finder does not require the client to register or provide any information in order to view our site. Should the client provide any personal information to the site for any reason, the clients privacy is completely guaranteed.

Personal Information means any information that may be used to determine an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit Philippinepetfinder.com Web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained.   
Philippine Pet Finder is aware of and sensitive to the privacy concerns of visitors to its website. Any information you provide to Philippine Pet Finder, when you request information, or use any of the other portions of our website, is securely maintained on our Web server and internal systems. This information may be used to provide you with information you've requested about our company and our services. Although Philippine Pet Finder has taken measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this policy.  
Philippine Pet Finder or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. We will maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of your Personally-Identifiable Information. All of our commerce forms are secure and are sent to us over a Secure Sockets Layer, which is using the highest encryption technology to ensure your information is not accessible by any third parties.  
The information that the site collect will not be used to create customer profiles based on browsing or purchasing history.  Philippine Pet Finder will not supplement information collected at this web site with data from other sources. Philippine Pet Finder will not share data with any third parties.  
Philippine Pet Finder offer links to other Web sites.  Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read  their privacy policies.  Their standards may differ from ours.

This web site offers forums.  Please be inform that information posted in these venues becomes public knowledge. All information is supplied by individuals listed and each is responsible for themselves.

Like many websites, Philippine Pet Finder use "cookies" to enhance the clients experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Cookies are small programs that enhance your use of the Internet, in general, and specifically Philippine Pet Finder use cookies to enhance your usage of our functions.

The Privacy Policy can be motified anytime without notice to the client.

Linet OI, Neff LL [cialis vs levitra](http://www.alabamageneric-cialis-online.info/?p=1 "india cialis"). Tell your doctor about all the prescription as well as over-the-counter medications you make use of [what cialis viagra do if and do taken together](http://buygenericcialislouisiana.info/?p=11 "buy cialis brand") Alcohol consumption can further lessen your high blood pressure and may increase certain uncomfortable side effects of Hyzaar [20mg cialis](http://floridabuy-generic-cialis-online.info/?p=23 "free pills coupon cialis 3").
